In congregation in the context of the aluminumic
You won't get this wrong any other guy I just want to tell you how I feel
I've got to make you understand Never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around it, he's ready to Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
We've known each other for so long Your heart's been aching, huh?
You're too shy to say it Is that we've all know what's been going on
We know the game I'm with Gonna play it And if you ask me how I feel
Don't tell me you're too bad to see Never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around it, he's ready to Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
Never gonna give you up Never gonna let you down Never gonna run around it, he's ready to
Never gonna make you cry Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
Never gonna give you up Never gonna give you up Never gonna give you up
Never gonna give, never gonna give We've known each other for so long
Your heart's been aching, huh? You're too shy to say it Is that we've all know what's been going on
We know the game I'm with Gonna play it And if I just wanna tell you how I feel
Don't tell me you're too bad to see Never gonna give you up, never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around it, he's ready to Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
Never gonna give you up Never gonna let you down Never gonna run around it, he's ready to Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you Never gonna give you up Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around it, he's ready to Never gonna make you cry Never gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you